<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>DockFlow</title>
        <item>
            <title>1.41</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:33:19 +0300</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>1.41</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.41</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>13.5</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
                https://appitstudio.github.io/dock-flow-updates/release-notes.html</sparkle:fullReleaseNotesLink>
            <description><![CDATA[
                <h2>What's New in DockFlow 1.41</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Enhanced Export and Import System</strong>
                        <ul>
                            <li><strong>Export without folders</strong> - Now the default method, perfect for sharing presets between different machines</li>
                            <li><strong>Selective preset management</strong> - Choose exactly which presets to export and import with full control</li>
                            <li><strong>Custom labeling system</strong> - Edit labels before exporting with separate private and public labels for better organization and sharing</li>
                            <li><strong>Smart app detection</strong> - Get notified when imported apps don't exist on your Mac, with direct download links provided for many apps</li>
                            <li><strong>Easy wizard UI</strong> - Streamlined, user-friendly interface guides you through both export and import processes</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li><strong>Modern Action Settings UI</strong>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Completely redesigned Action settings interface with a modern, intuitive design</li>
                            <li>Action icons now display directly in the edit preset screen next to each app that has an action configured</li>
                            <li>Enhanced usability and visual clarity for managing app-specific actions</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li><strong>UI/UX Improvements</strong>
                        <ul>
                            <li>Fixed various UI/UX bugs in light mode for better consistency</li>
                            <li>Multiple small fixes for improved overall look and behavior</li>
                            <li>Enhanced visual polish across the entire application</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <h3>Thank You!</h3>
                <p>These improvements make sharing and managing your DockFlow presets easier than ever. We appreciate your continued feedback and support!</p>
            ]]></description>
            <enclosure
                url="https://github.com/AppitStudio/dock-flow-updates/releases/download/prod/DockFlow.dmg"
                length="22024467" type="application/octet-stream"
                sparkle:edSignature="h5ZRTx2j9WEGkGWrFaWwOkoOHsVqN2HppLHHsW537NzU5ovyCEGhkt0Jc/rHAMRvGKQzXfIq0vfAnFj8IC+NDw==" />
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
